class DataBase {
  static List<Map> quizData = [
    {
      "question": "Q1. What is the capital city of Australia?",
      "option": [
        "Sydney",
        "Melbourne",
        "Canberra",
        "Perth",
      ],
      "answer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question": "Q2. Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
      "option": [
        "Venus",
        "Mars",
        "Jupiter",
        "Saturn",
      ],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question": "Q3. Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
      "option": [
        "Vincent van Gogh",
        "Leonardo da Vinci",
        "Pablo Picasso",
        "Michelangelo",
      ],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question": "Q4. Which country is famous for the Taj Mahal?",
      "option": [
        "India",
        "China",
        "Egypt",
        "Italy",
      ],
      "answer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question": "Q5. What is the largest ocean in the world?",
      "option": [
        "Atlantic Ocean",
        "Indian Ocean",
        "Pacific Ocean",
        "Arctic Ocean",
      ],
      "answer": 2,
    },
    {
      "question": "Q6. Who wrote the play Romeo and Juliet?",
      "option": [
        "William Shakespeare",
        "Jane Austen",
        "Charles Dickens",
        "Mark Twain",
      ],
      "answer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question": "Q7. Which country is known for the Great Wall?",
      "option": [
        "Japan",
        "China",
        "France",
        "Brazil",
      ],
      "answer": 1,
    },
    {
      "question": " Q8. What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
      "option": [
        "Au",
        "Ag",
        "Fe",
        "Cu",
      ],
      "answer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question": " Q9. Which animal is known as the King of the Jungle?",
      "option": [
        "Lion",
        "Tiger",
        "Elephant",
        "Gorilla",
      ],
      "answer": 0,
    },
    {
      "question": " Q10. Who invented the telephone?",
      "option": [
        "Alexander Graham Bell",
        "Thomas Edison",
        "Nikola Tesla",
        "Isaac Newton",
      ],
      "answer": 0,
    },
  ];
}
